(Penny:)All right.
Leonard fairly calls the question:
Who is in favor
of abandoning our game...
(Sheldon:)...and confronting
Penny's steroid-infused ex-boyfriend...
(Sheldon:)...in a suicidal mission
to extract money from him?
(Sheldon:)Say hi to Kurt for us.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Leonard:)When Frodo left the Shire
to take the one ring to Mordor...
...didn't Samwise, Pippin and Merry go?
- They did.
- Well?
(Sheldon:)They had a terrible time of it, Leonard.
(Raj:)Plus, no one stole their pants.
(Penny:)Fine.
(Leonard:)Enjoy your little game.
I'll make this quest on my own.
(Howard:)Leonard, wait.
Take a jacket, it's shpritzing a little.
(Leonard:)You guys suck.
Come on, please. He's so big.
- Okay, is everyone clear on the plan?
- Yes. Koothrappali's going to wet himself...
(Howard:)...I'm gonna throw up, Sheldon's
gonna run away, and you're going to die.